Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The National Society Daughters of the American Revolution QSOS
    - Kay Totten Huey oral history interview conducted by Geri Jackson, 2006-11-08 (Interview-id WV25309-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Quick questions, draft and final transcript, article, 8 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR487
  - The Nebraska QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Nebraska.
    - Karen Stiehl Osborn oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, April 18-20, 2007 (Interview-id NE68138-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NE68138_001_03.doc; afc2007009_NE68138_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_NE68138_001_02.jpg
    - Nao Nomura oral history interview conducted by Janneken Smucker, 2007-03-02 (Interview-id NE68508-001)
      JPN-001
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 2 digital documents, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NE68508_001_01.doc; afc2007009_NE68508_001_03.doc; afc2007009_NE68508_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR536; AFC 2007/009: SR537
  - The New Hampshire QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in New Hampshire.
    - Janet-Lee Santeusanio oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-08-05 (Interview-id NH03844-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NH03844_001_06.doc; afc2007009_NH03844_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_NH03844_001_04.jpg; afc2007009_NH03844_001_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NH03844_001_01.wav
  - The New Jersey QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in New Jersey.
    - Nancy Breland oral history interview conducted by Meg Cox, 2011-05-07 (Interview-id NJ08534-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NJ08534_001_01.doc; afc2007009_NJ08534_001_04.jpg; afc2007009_NJ08534_001_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 digital recordings; afc2007009_NJ08534_001_02.wav; afc2007009_NJ08534_001_03.wav
    - Meg Cox oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-08-03 (Interview-id NJ08540-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NJ08540_001_03.doc; afc2007009_NJ08540_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_NJ08540_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR673
  - The New Mexico QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in New Mexico.
    - Madge Lundy oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2007-05-17 (Interview-id NM87111-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NM87111_001_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR674
    - Ona Porterfield oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2007-11-06 (Interview-id NM87111-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NM87111_002_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR675
    - Margarete Brescia oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2007-12-05 (Interview-id NM87111-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NM87111_003_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_003_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR676
    - Janet MacDonald Moffatt oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2008-12-05 (Interview-id NM87111-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NM87111_004_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_004_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR727
    - Joyce Cummings Frashier oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2008-12-08 (Interview-id NM87111-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NM87111_005_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_005_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR728
    - Ann Dykhuizen Pitcher oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2008-12-11 (Interview-id NM87111-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NM87111_006_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_006_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR729
    - Evelyn Wade oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2009-05-12 (Interview-id NM87111-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NM87111_007_03.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_007_01.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_007_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR730
    - Lora Lloyd oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2009-05-13 (Interview-id NM87111-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NM87111_008_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_008_02.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_008_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR731
    - Carole Bonda oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2009-05-14 (Interview-id NM87111-009)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NM87111_009_01.doc; afc2007009_NM87111_009_02.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_009_03.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_009_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR732
    - Doris Jean Wilson De Gregorio oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2010-04-22 (Interview-id NM87111-010)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NM87111_010_04.docx; afc2007009_NM87111_010_01.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_010_02.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_010_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR774
    - Edwinna Rush Saucier oral history interview conducted by Evelyn Salinger, 2010-04-22 (Interview-id NM87111-011)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NM87111_011_03.docx; afc2007009_NM87111_011_01.jpg; afc2007009_NM87111_011_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR838
  - The New York QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in New York State.
    - Adrienne Yorinks oral history interview conducted by Bernard Herman, 2002-11-30 (Interview-id NY-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, promotional materials (including color cards and a poster)
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR389; AFC 2007/009: SR390
    - Teresa Barkley oral history interview conducted by Bernard Herman, 2003-04-21 (Interview-id NY-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 6 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR391 - SR396
    - Marilyn Henrion oral history interview conducted by Amy Henderson, 2005-11-05 (Interview-id NY10012-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 6 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital image; afc2007009_NY10012_001_01.tif
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR397
    - Marilyn Henrion oral history interview conducted by Amy Henderson, 2005-11-05 (Interview-id NY10012-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, travel information, notes, 30 b/w printouts (from digital images); 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY10012_002_01.tif; afc2007009_NY10012_002_02.tif
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR398
    - Victoria Findlay Wolfe oral history interview conducted by Meg Cox, 2011-08-05 (Interview-id NY10018-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NY10018_001_01.docx; afc2007009_NY10018_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_NY10018_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_NY10018_001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NY10018_001_05.wav
    - Michael Michalski oral history interview conducted by Amy Milne, 2011-04-27 (Interview-id NY11215-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NY11215_001._02.doc; afc2007009_NY11215_001._03.jpg; afc2007009_NY11215_001._04.jpg; afc2007009_NY11215_001._05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NY11215_001._01.wav
    - Jude Hill oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2010-01-08 (Interview-id NY11721-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NY11721_001_06.doc; afc2007009_NY11721_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_NY11721_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_NY11721_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NY11721_001_04.wav
    - M. Joan Lintault oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2005-07-13 (Interview-id NY12561-001)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR617
    - Holly Knott oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-05-18 (Interview-id NY13108-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Zylpha Siudara oral history interview conducted by Elizabeth Davis, 2003-06-02 (Interview-id NY14543-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, transcript, 8 4x6 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR400
    - Mildred Simpson oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2006-05-18 (Interview-id NY14722-001A)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY14722_001A_01.doc; afc2007009_NY14722_001A_02.jpg; afc2007009_NY14722_001A_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR401
    - Mildred Simpson oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2006-05-18 (Interview-id NY14722-001B)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document; afc2007009_NY14722_001B_01.doc
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR402
    - Kathleen Yaw oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2006-05-18 (Interview-id NY14722-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, “The Truth From Above” (song), 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR403
    - Joyce Brasted oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2006-06-13 (Interview-id NY14722-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR404
    - Louise Quick oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2007-10-09 (Interview-id NY14722-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY14722_004_01.doc; afc2007009_NY14722_004_02.jpg; afc2007009_NY14722_004_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR577
    - Pauline Fisher oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2007-10-09 (Interview-id NY14722-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY14722_005_03.doc; afc2007009_NY14722_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_NY14722_005_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR791
    - Marcia Wethli oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2007-10-09 (Interview-id NY14722-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY14722_006_03.doc; afc2007009_NY14722_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_NY14722_006_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR677
    - Helen Sager oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2007-10-09 (Interview-id NY14722-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY14722_007_03.doc; afc2007009_NY14722_007_01.jpg; afc2007009_NY14722_007_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR678
    - Pat Knable oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2007-09-10 (Interview-id NY14722-008)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NY14722_008_03.doc; afc2007009_NY14722_008_01.jpg; afc2007009_NY14722_008_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR679
    - Marion Hiller oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2006-05-18 (Interview-id NY14787-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR405
  - The North Carolina QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in North Carolina.
    - Scott Murkin oral history interview conducted by Tomme Fent, 2005-10-01 (Interview-id NC27205-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, CD instructions, 2 color printouts (from digital images), 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)
    - Delores Hamilton oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-07-21 (Interview-id NC27518-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Keisha Roberts oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-08-05 (Interview-id NC27607-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NC27607_001_01.doc; afc2007009_NC27607_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR539
    - Marni Goldshlag oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, June 27 - 30, 2006 (Interview-id NC27704-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
    - Selena Sullivan oral history interview conducted by Le Rowell, 2008-02-09 (Interview-id NC27707-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NC27707_001_03.doc; afc2007009_NC27707_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_NC27707_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR667
    - Nancy G Cook oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-04-21 (Interview-id NC28270-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_NC28270_001_02.doc; afc2007009_NC28270_001_01.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NC28270_001_03.wav
    - Laura Nelle Goebel oral history interview conducted by Suzanne Hill McDowell, 2011-07-27 (Interview-id NC28779-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_NC28779_001_06.doc; afc2007009_NC28779_001_02-05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NC28779_001_01.wav
    - Norma Bradley oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-02-17 (Interview-id NC28805-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Pamphlet, transcript, 1 b/w printout-3 images, 1 color printout; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_NC28805_001_04.doc; afc2007009_NC28805_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_NC28805_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_NC28805_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NC28805_001_05.wav
  - The North Dakota QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in North Dakota.
    - Kimberlee Madsen oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-08-28 (Interview-id ND58802-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_ND58802_001_03.doc; afc2007009_ND58802_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ND58802_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_ND58802_001_04.wav
  - The Ohio QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Ohio.
    - Susan Shie oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, October 1-5, 2006 (Interview-id OH44691-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_OH44691_001_03.doc; afc2007009_OH44691_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH44691_001_02.jpg
    - Lisa Quintana oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-19 (Interview-id OH45373-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH45373_001_06.doc; afc2007009_OH45373_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH45373_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH45373_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH45373_001_04.wav
    - Maria Elkins oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2006-06-10 (Interview-id OH45432-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR406
  - The Ohio Quilts!! QSOS
    Karen Musgrave, QSOS volunteer, conducted interviews at the 2008 National Quilting Association, Inc. meeting in Columbus, Ohio, of Ohio Quilts!! members. Ohio Quilts!! is a community of quiltmakers and quilt enthusiasts dedicated to educating the public and its members by offering the opportunity to network with others across Ohio.
    - Maxine Groves oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-06-18 (Interview-id OH43212-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_OH43212_001_05.doc; afc2007009_OH43212_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43212_001_03.wav
    - Donna Sue Groves oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-06-18 (Interview-id OH43212-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_OH43212_002_01.doc; afc2007009_OH43212_002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43212_002_03.wav
    - Irene Goodrich oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-06-19 (Interview-id OH43212-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_OH43212_003_05.doc; afc2007009_OH43212_003_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_003_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43212_003_03.wav
    - Irene Goodrich oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-06-19 (Interview-id OH43212-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43212_004_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43212_004_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_004_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_004_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43212_004_04.wav
    - Teri Henderson Tope oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-06-20 (Interview-id OH43212-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43212_005_04.doc; afc2007009_OH43212_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_005_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_005_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43212_005_05.wav
    - Jennifer McCann oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2008-06-20 (Interview-id OH43212-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout-3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43212_006_04.doc; afc2007009_OH43212_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_006_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43212_006_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43212_006_05.wav
  - The Ohio Reformatory for Women Quilt QSOS
    Karen Musgrave, QSOS volunteer, traveled to Marysville, Ohio, to interview quiltmakers who had participated in a special Sacred Threads exhibit. Many of the women interviewed were first time quiltmakers.
    - Joy Major oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-20 (Interview-id OH43040-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43040_001_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_001_04.wav
    - Rosa Angulo oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-20 (Interview-id OH43040-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43040_002_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_002_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_002_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_002_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_002_04.wav
    - Jami Burns oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-20 (Interview-id OH43040-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout; 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_OH43040_003_01.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_003_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_003_03.wav
    - Michelle Owens oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-20 (Interview-id OH43040-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43040_004_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_004_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_004_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_004_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_004_04.wav
    - Teresa Romano oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-20 (Interview-id OH43040-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43040_005_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_005_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_005_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_005_04.wav
    - Rhonda Edwards oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-20 (Interview-id OH43040-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43040_006_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_006_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_006_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_006_04.wav
    - Tangie Thomas oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-07-21 (Interview-id OH43040-007)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_OH43040_007_06.doc; afc2007009_OH43040_007_01.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_007_02.jpg; afc2007009_OH43040_007_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH43040_007_04.wav
  - The Oklahoma QSOS
    QSOS volunteers conducted interviews with quiltmakers in Oklahoma.
    - Carol Ann Sinnreich oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-10-07 (Interview-id OK73507-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_OK73507_001_05.doc; afc2007009_OK73507_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_OK73507_001_02.jpg